(Raj:)Go ahead, make fun.
(Raj:)You can't embarrass me.
(Raj:)I've got a beautiful
girlfriend
(Raj:)and a dog who loves me so much
she drinks my bathwater.
(Howard:)Okay, who was he talking to,
Emily or Cinnamon:
"I want you to know,
the bed feels so lonely
when you're not in it."
(Raj:)I may not be liking
this game so much.
(Howard:)Cinnamon.
Give me another one.
Okay, Emily or Cinnamon:
"Check it out,
I got us matching sweaters!"
(Leonard:)We all got the Christmas card--
Cinnamon.
(Raj:)You know, a man can care deeply
about a woman and a pet.
(Raj:)It's not strange.
(Leonard:)Ooh, Emily.
(Leonard:)I heard him say that
to Emily.
(Leonard:)Hey, I thought
you were staying home.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I was, but after
talking to Penny,
I realized something.
(Sheldon:)I... first, she's trying much
harder to stay attractive